{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Dà",
      "answer": "大"
    },
    {
      "question": "Duōshǎo",
      "answer": "多少"
    },
    {
      "question": "Duō",
      "answer": "多"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shǎo",
      "answer": "少"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xǐhuān",
      "answer": "喜欢"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wàiyǔ",
      "answer": "外语"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wài",
      "answer": "外"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yǔ",
      "answer": "语"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wàiguó",
      "answer": "外国"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bái",
      "answer": "白"
    }
  ]
}
